

# **NIKOLAAS DAEM**

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

# PERSONAL PROFILE

Confident, highly organised and passionate about developing software. Keen on learning and expanding my knowledge in various fields within the IT industry. Bringing forth several years of experience in a lead position at youth movements and work fields.

# EDUCATION

Java Developer IOT @ INTEC BRUSSEL

# **PROJECTS**

https://github.com/DaemNE

#### LANGUAGES

# CONTACT

- Ŷ
- ☑ NikolaasDaem@hotmail.com
- **C**
- in /nikolaasdaem

#### IT-SKILLS

- Proficiënt in / with: Java, Python, SQL & MYSQL, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Spring, JDBC,
- Software: Excel, Word

#### SKILLS

- Exceptional communication and networking skills
- Successful working in a team environment, as well as independently
- The ability to work under pressure and multi-task
- Listening and following instructions and deliver quality results
- Not afraid to ask for help when stuck

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

### **Environment Brussel.**, Events Assistant

FEB 2020 - FEB 2021

- Organized and supported multiple events
- Constantly updated the company's policies concerning the corona virus
- Monitored the agenda of our rooms to rent
- S.P.O.C. for our clients and our partners

#### McDonalds., Versatile employee

2018 - 2019

Versatile tasks

#### **Private tutoring - Dutch classes**

2018 - 2019

• Tutored children of ages 6-10

# EXTRA-CURRICULAR

**CHIRO Schaarbeek., Managing Leader** 

2019 - NOW

**CHIRO Ganshoren., Member + Leader** 

2003 - 2018